Narrator: Breakfast
A: bread
Narrator: 12
A: butter
Narrator: 7
A: cereal
Narrator: 1
A: cheese
Narrator: 6
A: coffee
A: eggs
Narrator: 3
A: jam
Narrator: 4
A: juice
Narrator: 8
A: milk
Narrator: 10
A: sugar
Narrator: 2
A: tea
Narrator: 5
A: toast
Narrator: Lunch or dinner
Narrator: 18
B: fish, for example, salmon, tuna
Narrator: 17
B: herbs
Narrator: 15
B: meat, for example, chicken, sausages, steak
Narrator: 14
B: oil
Narrator: 21
B: pasta
Narrator: 27
B: rice
Narrator: 26
B: salad
Narrator: 23
B: seafood
Narrator: 28
B: spices
Narrator: Vegetables
A: carrots
Narrator: 16
A: French fries
Narrator: 13
A: lettuce
Narrator: 30
A: mushrooms
Narrator: 20
A: onions
Narrator: 24
A: peas
Narrator: 19
A: peppers
Narrator: 22
A: potatoes
Narrator: 25
A: tomatoes
Narrator: Fruit
Narrator: 41
B: apples
Narrator: 39
B: bananas
Narrator: 35
B: oranges
Narrator: 32
B: a pineapple
Narrator: 36
B: strawberries
Narrator: Desserts
A: cake
Narrator: 38
A: fruit salad
Narrator: 33
A: ice cream
Narrator: Snacks
B: candy
Narrator: 42
B: chocolate
Narrator: 37
B: cookies
Narrator: 40
B: nuts
Narrator: 34
B: potato chips
Narrator: 31
B: a sandwich